这边走  妹子们
Right this way, ladies.
现在往左看  这次游览的重头戏
And now to our left, the highlight of the tour.
丽芙·鲁尼的闺房
Liv rooney's sleeping chamber.
请不要越过房间属于丽芙的那头
Please do not disturb liv's side of the room.
但是没啥名气的她双胞胎的床就随便站
But feel free to stand on the un-famous twin's bed
还能照张相
And take a picture.
这和我想象的别无二致
It's exactly how I imagined it.
当代的都市公主啊
Urban princess contemporary.
花多少钱能让我过了这条鹅绒围栏
How much to get me past the velvet rope?
抱歉  亚蒂
Sorry, Artie.
这是禁止入内的
That is off-limits.
10 美元
10 bucks.
能让我享受一下明星风范的话给你 20 美元
I'll give you 20 if I can have a diva moment.
成交
Deal.
我很想开开眼
I really want to see this.
你确定这是个好主意么
Are you sure this is a good idea?
帕克  我认为这一切都不是个好主意
Parker, I'm not sure any of this is a good idea.
预备
Ready?
丽芙与亚蒂要白头偕老
Liv and artie forever!
我实在是太想取笑一下了
I really want to make fun of that.
但是那确实是才气不浅啊
But it was nothing short of magnificent.